Hello everyone and welcome to EnglishPod.
大家好，欢迎收听EnglishPod。
My name is Marco.
我是Marco。
My name is Kathryn and today we have a very, very useful intermediate level lesson for
我是Kathryn，今天我们为大家带来一节非常非常实用的中级课程，内容是关于
you all about the weather.
天气的。
That's right.
没错。
So obviously we have seen the news and sometimes on the news we have the weather report.
显然我们都看过新闻，有时新闻里会有天气预报。
So today we're going to learn all about that weather report in English.
所以今天我们要学习如何用英语描述天气预报。
So let's check out today's dialogue and we'll be back in a moment to talk about the words
我们先来看看今天的对话，稍后再回来讨论那些
and phrases that those weather forecasters used.
天气预报员使用的词汇和短语。
And those are today's top stories.
以上就是今天的头条新闻。
Now let's go to John for the weather.
现在让我们连线John来播报天气。
John, what does the forecast look like for our weekend travelers?
John，对于周末出行的旅客，天气预报怎么说？
I'm afraid we're in for a rough weekend, Mary.
恐怕这个周末不太好过，Mary。
There's a storm system moving through the East Coast.
有一个风暴系统正在东海岸移动。
It will be drizzling all day today and there's a 60% chance of thunderstorms this evening.
今天全天会有毛毛雨，今晚有60%的几率出现雷暴。
It will be warm and humid all weekend.
整个周末都会温暖而潮湿。
In the Midwest, expect strong winds and a low of around 40 degrees.
在中西部地区，预计会有强风，最低气温大约40华氏度。
That's pretty chilly for the summer.
夏天来说这相当冷了。
Will it rain on Saturday?
周六会下雨吗？
Unfortunately, yes.
不幸的是，会的。
It will be clear early Saturday morning, but there is a high chance of showers and thunderstorms
周六清晨天气会放晴，但当天晚些时候有很高的概率出现阵雨和雷暴
later in the day.
。
There is a severe thunderstorm warning for some parts of the Southeast.
东南部部分地区有强雷暴警报。
Folks in those areas might see some hail and flooding, especially in areas that have been
那些地区的居民可能会看到冰雹和洪水，尤其是在那些
experiencing record high rainfalls.
降雨量创纪录的地区。
That certainly sounds like a dreary Saturday.
听起来周六确实是个阴沉的日子。
It gets better on Sunday, though.
不过周日会好转。
The storm systems move east and the skies will clear up at night.
风暴系统向东移动，夜间天空会放晴。
It will still be rather cool with highs in the low 50s.
天气仍然相当凉爽，最高气温在50华氏度出头。
The West Coast will be experiencing some unusually chilly weather, but at least the sun will
西海岸将经历异常寒冷的天气，但至少太阳会
come out.
出来。
I advise weekend travelers to be careful, especially while driving.
我建议周末出行的旅客要小心，尤其是开车时。
Back to you, Mary.
交回给你，Mary。
Thanks, John.
谢谢，John。
And there you have it.
以上就是天气预报。
Looks like it's a weekend to stay at home.
看来这个周末适合待在家里。
All right, we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
So apparently, they're not going to have great weather this weekend and they actually started
显然，他们这个周末天气不太好，而且他们一开始
with an interesting word.
用了一个有趣的词。
And actually, the commentator started with asking the weatherman, John, what does the
实际上，主持人一开始问天气预报员John：“对于我们的周末，天气预报
forecast look like for our weekend?
怎么说？”
Okay, so the word here, forecast, is very, very important because it describes this part
好的，这里的“forecast”这个词非常重要，因为它描述了新闻播报的
of the newscast.
这一部分。
A forecast is basically a prediction or a description of the future weather situation.
预报基本上是对未来天气情况的预测或描述。
That's right.
没错。
So we're talking about the weather forecast.
所以我们说的是天气预报。
Now it's very interesting because we can also use that in business, for example, in budgets.
有趣的是，这个词也可以用在商业中，比如预算。
You can say, what is the financial forecast of the company?
你可以说：“公司的财务预测是什么？”
All right, so you can't know what will happen, but you can predict it and that's what a forecast
好的，你无法知道会发生什么，但你可以预测，这就是
is.
预报。
That's right.
没错。
So we're talking about the weather forecast and the weatherman said that, well, there
所以我们说的是天气预报，天气预报员说，嗯，
are some storms coming and it will be drizzling all day.
有些风暴要来了，而且会下一整天的毛毛雨。
Okay, so to drizzle is a verb and it's like the verb to rain, except it's less by degree.
好的，“drizzle”是一个动词，和“rain”这个动词类似，只是程度更轻。
So it's very light rain.
所以是非常小的雨。
Yeah, it's kind of like if I spray you with water from a spray can or something, it's
是的，有点像我用喷水壶喷你水，那就是
like drizzle.
毛毛雨。
It's just little dots of water.
只是小水珠。
It's not like you're getting wet.
不像你会被淋湿。
You don't really have the normal heavy raindrops.
没有那种正常的大雨滴。
You just have a little bit of water coming down.
只有一点点水落下来。
But it's annoying because do you bring your umbrella?
但很烦人，因为你要不要带伞？
Do you leave your umbrella?
要不要不带伞？
So drizzling is a kind of rain that's very, very light.
所以“drizzling”是一种非常非常小的雨。
That's right.
没错。
All right, so it's going to drizzle all day and the weatherman also said that we might
好的，所以会下一整天毛毛雨，天气预报员还说我们可能
have some thunderstorms.
会有雷暴。
Okay, so thunderstorms are very different.
好的，雷暴非常不同。
Thunderstorms are a kind of storm where there is thunder.
雷暴是一种有雷声的风暴。
So thunder is the loud noises when there's lightning.
所以“thunder”是闪电时发出的巨响。
Lightning, okay.
闪电，好的。
So lightning is like the flash that you get from the sky and thunder is the hard sound
所以“lightning”是天空中出现的闪光，“thunder”是之后
that comes after.
发出的巨响。
The boom.
轰隆声。
That's right.
没错。
Yeah, so remember light, lightning.
是的，记住“light”和“lightning”。
Light is the light that comes down from the sky, lightning.
“Light”是从天空下来的光，“lightning”是闪电。
And thunderstorms are just those loud noises that the lightning makes.
而“thunderstorms”就是闪电发出的那些巨响。
So usually with thunderstorms, we have very heavy rain.
所以通常雷暴会伴随非常大的雨。
That's right.
没错。
And that's why it's different from drizzling, which is very light.
这就是为什么它和毛毛雨不同，毛毛雨非常小。
Okay.
好的。
Now we're talking about water.
现在我们说的是水。
We have drizzle, we have thunderstorm.
我们有毛毛雨，有雷暴。
Now what about a shower?
那阵雨呢？
Because the weatherman said there is a high chance of showers.
因为天气预报员说阵雨的可能性很大。
Well, yes, there's a high chance of showers.
嗯，是的，阵雨的可能性很大。
I take showers every day, thank you very much.
我每天都洗澡，非常感谢。
But that's not the kind of shower we're talking about here, is it?
但这不是我们这里说的那种阵雨，对吧？
That's right.
没错。
Think about it though.
不过想想看。
It's similar.
它们很相似。
A shower when you wash yourself is water coming down on top of you.
你洗澡时，水是从头顶落下来的。
Well, in this case, it's a rain shower.
嗯，在这种情况下，它是降雨阵雨。
So it's rain that's happening.
所以就是正在下的雨。
Okay, so it's rain water that's coming down, very similar to the shower that you take in
好的，所以是雨水落下来，和你早上洗澡非常相似。
the morning.
早上。
The difference though is that a shower is a noun and to rain is a verb.
区别在于，“阵雨”是名词，“下雨”是动词。
So it will rain tomorrow or we expect showers tomorrow.
所以明天会下雨，或者我们预计明天有阵雨。
Both mean the same thing.
两者意思相同。
All right.
好的。
Very good.
非常好。
And well, talking about showers and thunderstorms, there's also another type of water that falls
嗯，说到阵雨和雷暴，还有另一种从天上落下的水。
from the sky.
从天上。
This is called hail.
这叫做冰雹。
Okay.
好的。
And hail is difficult to describe because it's like ice, but it's not really.
冰雹很难描述，因为它像冰，但又不完全是。
It's just usually hard, almost like marbles, like hard balls of rain that come down.
它通常很硬，几乎像弹珠，像硬邦邦的雨球落下来。
So it's not snow.
所以它不是雪。
That's right.
没错。
It hurts when it hits you.
打到你身上会很疼。
Sometimes it's very big, sometimes it's very small, but it's heavy, hard things that come
有时很大，有时很小，但它是从云里落下的又重又硬的东西。
out of the clouds.
从云里。
Yeah.
是的。
So just think about it.
所以想想看。
It's very, very similar to ice.
它和冰非常非常相似。
It's the small pieces of ice coming down from the sky.
是从天上落下的小冰块。
So that's hail.
那就是冰雹。
Obviously, very different from snow because as we said, it's hard.
显然，和雪很不一样，因为正如我们所说，它是硬的。
Snow is very soft.
雪很软。
Yes.
是的。
And well, with this type of weather going on in the weekend, the commentator said, wow,
嗯，周末有这样的天气，评论员说，哇，那听起来确实是个沉闷的星期六。
that certainly sounds like a dreary Saturday.
那听起来确实是个沉闷的星期六。
Okay.
好的。
Dreary is a great word to describe it.
“沉闷”是个很好的词来形容它。
So as you can tell, it's going to rain.
所以你可以看出，要下雨了。
Dreary is not a good thing.
“沉闷”不是好事。
It's not a happy thing.
不是开心的事。
Okay.
好的。
So something is dreary when it's not very exciting.
所以某样东西沉闷，就是它不太令人兴奋。
It looks like it'll be dull or sad or boring or dark.
看起来会阴郁、悲伤、无聊或黑暗。
Now can you describe a person like this as well?
你也可以这样形容一个人吗？
Yes.
可以。
He's a very dreary person.
他是个很沉闷的人。
He's never optimistic.
他从不乐观。
He's always down and yeah, kind of quiet and sad and down.
他总是情绪低落，嗯，有点安静、悲伤和消沉。
Boring.
无聊。
Yeah.
是的。
Okay.
好的。
So that's what it means.
这就是它的意思。
Something that's boring, not very exciting or very calm.
某样东西无聊、不太令人兴奋或很平静。
But also dark.
但也有黑暗的一面。
There's a dark element to it because something is dreary.
因为沉闷的东西带有黑暗元素。
You know, there's no sunshine.
你知道，没有阳光。
There's no light.
没有光亮。
There's no optimism.
没有乐观情绪。
So you can say it's a dreary day.
所以你可以说这是个沉闷的日子。
Yeah.
是的。
Very dreary day today.
今天非常沉闷。
No light, no sunshine.
没有光亮，没有阳光。
Okay.
好的。
Very good.
非常好。
So we've taken a look at a lot of vocab there.
所以我们看了很多词汇。
Why don't we review what we've just learned and listen to the dialogue again.
我们为什么不复习一下刚学的内容，再听一遍对话呢。
And those are today's top stories.
那些是今天的头条新闻。
Now let's go to John for the weather.
现在让我们去找约翰看天气。
John, what does the forecast look like for our weekend travelers?
约翰，我们周末出行的人，天气预报怎么样？
I'm afraid we're in for a rough weekend, Mary.
恐怕我们周末要遭罪了，玛丽。
There's a storm system moving through the East Coast.
有一个风暴系统正在穿过东海岸。
It will be drizzling all day today and there's a 60% chance of thunderstorms this evening.
今天一整天都会下毛毛雨，今晚有60%的可能性出现雷暴。
It will be warm and humid all weekend.
整个周末都会温暖潮湿。
In the Midwest, expect strong winds and a low of around 40 degrees.
在中西部，预计会有强风，最低气温大约40度。
That's pretty chilly for the summer.
夏天来说这挺凉的。
Will it rain on Saturday?
星期六会下雨吗？
Unfortunately, yes.
不幸的是，会下。
It will be clear early Saturday morning, but there is a high chance of showers and thunderstorms
星期六早上会放晴，但下午有很高的概率出现阵雨和雷暴，
later in the day.
晚些时候。
There is a severe thunderstorm warning for some parts of the Southeast.
东南部部分地区有强雷暴警报。
Folks in those areas might see some hail and flooding, especially in areas that have been
那些地区的居民可能会遇到冰雹和洪水，尤其是在那些
experiencing record high rainfalls.
降雨量创纪录的地区。
That certainly sounds like a dreary Saturday.
这听起来确实是个沉闷的星期六。
It gets better on Sunday, though.
不过星期天会好转。
The storm systems move East and the skies will clear up at night.
风暴系统向东移动，天空将在夜间放晴。
It will still be rather cool with highs in the low 50s.
天气仍然相当凉爽，最高气温在50华氏度出头。
The West Coast will be experiencing some unusually chilly weather, but at least the sun will
西海岸将经历一些异常寒冷的天气，但至少太阳会
come out.
出来。
I advise weekend travelers to be careful, especially while driving.
我建议周末旅行者要小心，尤其是开车时。
Back to you, Mary.
交回给你，玛丽。
Thanks, John.
谢谢，约翰。
And there you have it.
以上就是天气预报。
Looks like it's a weekend to stay at home.
看来这是个待在家里的周末。
All right.
好了。
We're back.
我们回来了。
So now, we're going to talk a little bit about some phrases that we've chosen for you on
现在，我们要聊聊我们为你们挑选的一些短语，在
Fluency Builder.
流利度构建环节。
So when we're talking about forecasts, remember that we're talking about things that aren't
所以当我们谈论天气预报时，记住我们说的是不确定的事情。
certain.
不确定。
We have to explain that there is a possibility of rain or a possibility of sunshine.
我们必须解释有可能下雨或有可能出太阳。
And usually, in the weather report, they will use percentages to describe how likely something
通常，在天气预报中，他们会用百分比来描述某事发生的
is to happen.
可能性。
That's right.
没错。
The weatherman said there is a 60% chance of thunderstorms.
天气预报员说有60%的概率会有雷暴。
OK.
好的。
So 60% is not very likely, but it's also not unlikely.
所以60%不是非常可能，但也不是不可能。
It means that it might happen that it rains.
这意味着可能会下雨。
That's right.
没错。
So as you said, it's a way to measure what the probabilities are.
所以就像你说的，这是一种衡量概率的方法。
Because imagine if the weatherman says it might rain tomorrow, you're like, well, maybe
因为想象一下，如果天气预报员说明天可能下雨，你会想，嗯，也许
it really will, or maybe it's very unlikely that it won't, or we don't really know.
真的会下，或者也许不太可能不下，或者我们真的不知道。
Exactly.
正是。
So for example, if the weatherman says there's a 95% chance of rain tomorrow, do you bring
所以举个例子，如果天气预报员说明天有95%的概率下雨，你会带
your umbrella?
伞吗？
Yes.
会。
What if he says there's a 5% chance of rain tomorrow?
如果他说明天有5%的概率下雨呢？
No.
不会。
So you have to think about the probability.
所以你得考虑概率。
60%, it's maybe half and half.
60%，大概是一半一半。
But 95%, it's very likely to happen.
但95%，就非常可能发生。
That's right.
没错。
And he also mentioned there's a high chance of thunderstorms, or maybe you can say there's
他还提到有很高的概率会有雷暴，或者你也可以说有
a low chance of hail.
很低的概率下冰雹。
Right.
对。
So he's basically saying, he or she is basically saying, you know, it's possible that this
所以他或她基本上是在说，你知道，这件事可能发生，
will happen, or it's not likely this will happen.
或者这件事不太可能发生。
They're trying to help you out.
他们是在帮你。
They can't say this will happen, because they don't know.
他们不能说一定会发生，因为他们不知道。
OK.
好的。
So the key word for probability here, the key word is chance.
所以这里概率的关键词是“机会”。
There is a good chance that it will rain.
很有可能下雨。
So chance is probability.
所以“机会”就是概率。
Right.
对。
So for example, what's the chance it will rain tomorrow?
所以举个例子，明天下雨的机会有多大？
Well, there's a high chance.
嗯，机会很大。
OK.
好的。
Very good.
非常好。
OK.
好的。
And now when we talk about the degrees, or how warm or cold it is, so we express it in
现在当我们谈论温度，或者有多暖或多冷时，我们在一些国家用华氏度表示，
Fahrenheit in some countries, or in other countries in centigrade.
在其他国家用摄氏度表示。
Here we talk about 40 degrees Fahrenheit.
这里我们说的是40华氏度。
But the weatherman also says highs and lows.
但天气预报员也提到了最高温和最低温。
There's a low of around 40 degrees.
最低气温大约40度。
What does he mean, a low?
他说的最低温是什么意思？
This is a really important part of the forecast, because you need to know, will you have to
这是天气预报中非常重要的一部分，因为你需要知道，明天你需不需要
bring a coat tomorrow?
带外套？
Is it going to be hot or cold?
天气会热还是冷？
And so you think about a day, usually during the day at noon, or 1 o'clock in the afternoon,
所以你想一下一天中，通常在中午或下午1点，
it's the hottest.
是最热的。
But at night, it's the coldest.
但晚上是最冷的。
And so the low refers to the lowest temperature, and the high refers to the highest temperature.
所以低温指的是最低温度，高温指的是最高温度。
So for example, in the fall, maybe the highs are 60 degrees, but the lows are 40.
比如在秋天，高温可能是60度，但低温是40度。
So you should bring a coat.
所以你应该带件外套。
OK.
好的。
It means at night, it'll be 40, and during the day, it'll be 60.
意思是晚上会是40度，白天会是60度。
OK.
好的。
So we're talking about the highs are the highest temperatures, or the highest number that we'll
所以我们说的是高温是最高温度，或者我们会达到的最高数值，
get, and the lows is the lowest.
而低温是最低数值。
So the weatherman will commonly say, tomorrow we'll experience a high of 32 degrees and
所以天气预报员通常会说明天最高温度32度，
a low of 25.
最低温度25度。
Right.
对。
So it's very easy to understand that the temperature during the day will be between these two numbers.
所以很容易理解白天的温度会在这两个数字之间。
Right.
对。
Very good.
很好。
OK.
好的。
And for our last phrase, the weatherman also said that there is a severe thunderstorm warning
至于我们最后一个短语，天气预报员还说东南部部分地区有
for some parts of the Southeast.
强雷暴警报。
All right.
好的。
So, Marco, this is a really key phrase, because it's telling people about potential danger.
所以，Marco，这确实是一个关键短语，因为它是在告诉人们潜在的危险。
You know, a thunderstorm can be very dangerous, so you want to stay inside.
你知道，雷暴可能非常危险，所以你应该待在室内。
So a severe thunderstorm warning, severe means very, very serious, is something you should
所以强雷暴警报，severe意思是极其严重，是你应该
pay attention to.
注意的事情。
That's right.
没错。
But now, the interesting thing is that we can change the noun, in this case, thunderstorm,
但有趣的是，我们可以改变名词，这里用的是雷暴，
and we can talk about, for example, a severe tornado warning.
我们可以说，比如，强龙卷风警报。
All right.
好的。
So if there's a severe tornado warning, then I really have to pay attention to the weather
所以如果有强龙卷风警报，那我真的得注意天气，
and be careful not to go outside.
小心不要出门。
Or even a severe flood warning.
或者甚至强洪水警报。
You need to know that the streets might become flooded and prepare.
你需要知道街道可能会被淹，并做好准备。
So they're saying that there's a very high probability that this might happen, so they're
所以他们是在说这种情况发生的可能性很高，所以他们
warning you to take precaution.
警告你要采取预防措施。
All right.
好的。
So pay attention to that last one.
所以注意最后一个。
And we're going to listen to today's dialogue one more time.
我们将再听一遍今天的对话。
We'll be back in a moment to talk a little bit more about the weather.
我们一会儿回来再聊更多关于天气的话题。
And those are today's top stories.
以上就是今天的头条新闻。
Now let's go to John for the weather.
现在让我们连线约翰播报天气。
John, what does the forecast look like for our weekend travelers?
约翰，我们周末出行的旅客会遇上什么样的天气？
I'm afraid we're in for a rough weekend, Mary.
恐怕这个周末不好过，玛丽。
There's a storm system moving through the East Coast.
有一个风暴系统正在穿过东海岸。
It will be drizzling all day today, and there's a 60% chance of thunderstorms this evening.
今天全天会有毛毛雨，今晚有60%的可能性出现雷暴。
It will be warm and humid all weekend.
整个周末会温暖潮湿。
In the Midwest, expect strong winds and a low of around 40 degrees.
在中西部，预计会有强风，低温大约40度。
That's pretty chilly for the summer.
夏天来说这相当冷了。
Will it rain on Saturday?
星期六会下雨吗？
Unfortunately, yes.
不幸的是，会下。
It will be clear early Saturday morning, but there is a high chance of showers and thunderstorms
星期六早上会放晴，但白天晚些时候有很高的可能性出现阵雨和雷暴。
later in the day.
There is a severe thunderstorm warning for some parts of the Southeast.
东南部部分地区有强雷暴警报。
Folks in those areas might see some hail and flooding, especially in areas that have been
那些地区的人们可能会看到冰雹和洪水，尤其是在
experiencing record high rainfalls.
降雨量创纪录的地区。
That certainly sounds like a dreary Saturday.
那听起来确实是个阴沉的星期六。
It gets better on Sunday, though.
不过星期天会好转。
The storm systems move east and the skies will clear up at night.
风暴系统向东移动，晚上天空会放晴。
It will still be rather cool, with highs in the low 50s.
天气仍然相当凉爽，最高温度在50度出头。
The West Coast will be experiencing some unusually chilly weather, but at least the sun will
西海岸将经历一些异常寒冷的天气，但至少太阳会
come out.
出来。
I advise weekend travelers to be careful, especially while driving.
我建议周末出行的旅客要小心，尤其是开车时。
Back to you, Mary.
交回给你，玛丽。
Thanks, John.
谢谢，约翰。
And there you have it.
就是这样。
Looks like it's a weekend to stay at home.
看来这是个待在家里的周末。
All right.
好的。
So talking about the weather, it always seems like the weatherman is always wrong.
说到天气，似乎天气预报员总是出错。
Always.
总是。
It's like the opposite of what should happen.
就像结果总是相反。
That's right.
没错。
But you can't blame them because all they have is a computer and some sensors and they
但你不能怪他们，因为他们只有一台电脑和一些传感器，
have to guess about the weather and help people figure out what to do.
他们得猜测天气，帮助人们决定该做什么。
Have you ever experienced anything severe like a hard thunderstorm or maybe a tornado
你经历过像强雷暴或龙卷风之类的严重天气吗？
or something like this?
I have, actually, because I'm from Chicago.
我经历过，因为我来自芝加哥。
And in America, the middle of the country is called the tornado belt.
在美国，国家中部被称为龙卷风带。
That means it's a piece of land where tornadoes are very common.
意思是那是一片龙卷风很常见的土地。
And so in the fall and in the spring, we often have tornadoes.
所以在秋天和春天，我们经常有龙卷风。
And I've been in a couple of tornadoes myself.
我自己就经历过几次龙卷风。
Oh, wow.
哦，哇。
Have you seen them?
你看到它们了吗？
Yes.
是的。
Is it amazing to see?
看到它很震撼吗？
They're very scary.
它们非常可怕。
You're always running inside and locking yourself in the basement.
你总是跑进屋里，把自己锁在地下室。
It's very important to protect yourself in a tornado because it's very dangerous around
在龙卷风中保护自己非常重要，因为龙卷风周围区域非常危险，
the area of the tornado because the wind is so strong that trucks and cars and telephone
风力非常强，以至于卡车、汽车、电线杆
poles and big, big heavy objects can fly through the air and hurt people.
以及又大又重的物体都能在空中飞过，伤害到人。
And that's how most of the damage happens.
这就是大部分破坏发生的方式。
Okay, so this is interesting because a tornado is also considered a natural disaster.
好吧，这很有趣，因为龙卷风也被视为一种自然灾害。
But it's a weather phenomenon, whereas earthquakes are a natural disaster, but it's not part
但它是一种天气现象，而地震是自然灾害，却不属于
of the weather.
天气范畴。
No, yeah, you're right.
不，对，你说得对。
It's not something that it sweeps in and it leaves.
它不是那种席卷而来又离开的东西。
Like a flood, for example, all of the rain will come down and it will create a flood.
比如洪水，所有的雨降下来，就会形成洪水。
An earthquake is a natural disaster that's not weather related.
地震是一种与天气无关的自然灾害。
That's right.
没错。
Okay, interesting thing.
好吧，有趣的事情。
Maybe some of our listeners that live in a very cold area have experienced a heavy snowstorm.
也许我们一些住在非常寒冷地区的听众经历过暴风雪。
Like a blizzard.
比如暴风雪。
Or maybe people in a tropical area have experienced a hurricane.
或者热带地区的人可能经历过飓风。
So let us know if you've ever been in one of these weather related phenomenons.
所以请告诉我们，你是否经历过这些与天气相关的现象。
And also if you have any comments or questions, we're always at EnglishPod.com.
如果你有任何评论或问题，我们随时在EnglishPod.com上。
We hope to see you guys there.
我们希望能在那里见到你们。
All right.
好了。
Thanks for listening.
感谢收听。